Mss.B.L493
American Philosophical Society
- Correspondence, 7.0 Linear feet 17 upright boxes, 1 oversized folder, 1 digital record. (Box 1-17)
  - Telegram to John L[awrence] Le Conte, May 3, 1867; 8x5-1/4; Wright, W. W. (William Wierman) 1824-1882
    Wyandotte, Kan. D. 1p. (see Le Conte papers Asks that he be in Kansas as early as possible for the expedition will not start until the middle of the month. Originally B L493.3
  - Telegram to Jo[h]n [Lawrence] Le Conte, Philadelphia, May 3, 1867; 8x5-1/4; Wright, W. W. (William Wierman) 1824-1882
    Wyandotte, Kan. D. 1p. (see Le Conte papers Will be happy to have a physician accompany them on the expedition. Originally B L493.3
  - Letter to [John L. Le Conte], May 9, 1867; 8-1/4x5-1/4; Stout, Arthur B.
    San Francisco, A.L.S. 3p. (see Le Conte papers.) Real estate in California.
  - Power of attorney to Aubrey H. Smith, from John L. Le Conte and Helen G. Le Conte, May 15, 1867; 8 1/4" x 13 1/4"; Le Conte, John L. (John Lawrence), 1825-1883
    Philadelphia, D.S. 3p. and end. Seal.
  - Letter to [John L. Le Conte], July (?), 23, 1867; 8-1/4x5-1/4; Candèze, E. C. (Ernest Charles), 1827-1898
    Liége A.L.S. 3p. In French. (see Le Conte papers.) Hopes that they can visit, when he comes to Europe, next September.
  - Letter to [J.L. ?] Leconte, Aug. 8, 1867; 5" x 8"; Murray, Andrew, 1812-1878
    Kensington, A.L.S. 1p.
  - Letter to W.W. Wright, Oct. 5, 1867; 7 3/4" x 9 3/4"; Le Conte, John L. (John Lawrence), 1825-1883
    Fort Craig, N.M., A.Dr. of L.S. 2p.
  - Letter to W. W. Wright, Oct. 6, 1867; 10x8; Eichaltz, L. H.
    Ft. Craig, N.M., L.S.:L.H.Eichaltz and others. 2p. Copy (see Le Conte papers.) Letter of appreciation, upon his removal to another post.
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, Philadelphia, Nov. 10, 1867; 8-1/4x5; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889
    Columbus,O., A.L.S. 2p. (see Le Conte papers.) Will try to determine the age of the coal from his fossils. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to [J.L. ?] Le Conte, Nov. 11, 1867; 7 3/4" x 9 3/4"; Wright, W. W. (William Wierman) 1824-1882
  - Letter to John [L.] Le Conte, Philadelphia, Nov. 15, 1867; 8x5; Brush, George Jarvis, 1831-1912
    New Haven, A.L.S. 4p. (see Le Conte papers.) Concerning his writings on coal and the specimens he forwarded. Dana has his writings and will forward them. They will examine mineral specimens free of charge.
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, Nov. 19, 1867; 5" x 8"; Dana, James Dwight, 1813-1895
  - Letter to J[ohn L.] Le Conte, Nov. 20, 1867; 8x5; Meehan, Thomas, 1826-1901
    Germantown, Penna., A.L.S. 2p. (see Le Conte papers Will leave seeds for him at the Academy of Natural Sciences. Botany.
  - Letter to [J.L. ?] Le Conte, Nov. 23, 1867; 7 3/4" x 9 3/4"; Wright, W. W. (William Wierman) 1824-1882
  - Letter to John [L.] Le Conte, Nov. 25, 1867; 7-3/4x5; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889
    Columbus, O., A.L.S. 1p. (see Le Conte papers.) Has received fossils. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to [John L.] Le Conte, Nov. 30, 1867; 9-3/4x7-3/4; Wright, W. W. (William Wierman) 1824-1882
    St. Louis, A.L.S. 1p. (see Le Conte papers.) Concerning his survey and the report on coal fields around Denver, Col. Originally B L493.3
  - Letter to [John L. Le Conte], Dec. 1, 1867; 8x5; Meek, F. B. (Fielding Bradford), 1817-1876
    Washington, A.L.S. 3p. (see Le Conte papers Attempts to identify fossils from the Western sections of the U.S.
  - Letter to J[ohn] L. Le Conte, Philadelphia, Dec. 3, 1867; 8x5-1/4; Provancher, L. (Léon), 1820-1892
    Pontneuf, Canada, A.L.S. 2p. In French. (see Le Conte papers.) Concerning entomology.
  - Letter to J.C. Reiff, Dec. 7, 1867; 7 1/2" x 9 1/2"; Perry, John D., 1815-1895
    Philadelphia, Extract from L. 1p.
  - Letter to John D. Perry, St. Louis, Mo, Dec. 12, 1867; 12-1/4x7-3/4; Le Conte, John L. (John Lawrence), 1825-1883
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. Draft. (see Le Conte papers.) Concerning a report showing the geological and agricultural resources surveyed. Originally B L493.3
  - Letter to John D. Perry, Dec. 12, 1867; 7 3/4" x 10"; Le Conte, John L. (John Lawrence), 1825-1883
    Philadelphia, A.Dr. of L. 3p. and end.
  - Letter to John [L.] Le Conte, Dec. 18, 1867; 8x5; Brush, George Jarvis, 1831-1912
    New Haven, A.L.S. 4p.and list of specimens of minerals sent by J.L.Le Conte, 3p. (see Le Conte papers.) Mineralogy.
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, Dec. 20, 1867; 5" x 8"; Dana, James Dwight, 1813-1895
  - Letter to Jno. L. Le Conte, Dec. 24, 1867; 5" x 8"; Reiff, J. C.
    Philadelphia A.L.S. 1p.
  - Letter to [John L.] Le Conte, Dec. 26, 1867; 8x5; Wright, W. W. (William Wierman) 1824-1882
    Harrisburg, Pa., A.L.S. 1p. Enc.of newspaper clipping. (see Le Conte papers.) Forwards clipping for future reference. Originally B L493.3
  - Letter to [J.L. ?] Le Conte, Dec. 30, 1867; 5" x 8"; Wright, W. W. (William Wierman) 1824-1882
    York Springs, A.L.S. 3p.
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, Jan. 6, 1868; 7-3/4x6-1/4; Strachan, W. T.
    Lancaster, A.L.S. 2p. (see Le Conte papers.) Concerning mines and mining. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, Jan. 9, 1868; 8" x 10"; Sonne, Charles
  - Letter to [J.L. ?] Le Conte, Jan. 11, 1868; 5" x 8"; Wright, W. W. (William Wierman) 1824-1882
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, Jan. 25, 1868; 8" x 10"; Walsh, B. D. (Benjamin Dann), 1808-1869
  - Letter to John [L.] Le Conte, Jan. 28, 1868; 5" x 8"; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889
    Columbus, O., A.L.S. 4p.
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, Feb. 9, 1868; 8-1/4x5-1/4; Hunt, Thomas Sterry, 1826-1892
    Montreal, A.L.S. 2p. (see Le Conte papers.) Has been too busy to investigate the rock specimens, although he is very interested in them.
  - Letter to John L. LeConte, Feb. 13, 1868; Thomson, J. Edgar, (James Edgar), 1808-1874
  - Letter to John [L.] Le Conte, March 1, 1868; 5" x 8"; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889
    Columbus, O., A.L.S. 2p.
  - Letter to John L. Leconte, March 6, 1868; 5" x 8"; Sallé, Aug., (Auguste), 1820-1896
  - Letter to [J.L.] Leconte, March 28, 1868; 5" x 8"; Genth, F. A. (Frederick Augustus), 1820-1893
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, March 28, 1868; 7 1/2" x 9 3/4"; Union Pacific Railway, Eastern Division
    Philadelphia, A.L.S: J.C. Reiff, agent. 1p.
  - Letter to [John L. LeConte], Mar. 30, 1868; de Bouvauloir, H.
  - Letter to John [L.] Le Conte, April 9, 1868; 5" x 8"; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889
    Columbus,O. A.L.S. 2p.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte ?], April 10, 1868; 5" x 8"; Hagen, Hermann August, 1817-1893
  - Letter to John [L. Le Conte ?], April 12, 1868; 5" x 8"; Harden, Jane LeConte
    Savannah, A.L.S. 4p.
  - Letter to [John L. LeConte], May 1, 1868; Hagen, Hermann August, 1817-1893
  - Letter to [J.L.] Leconte, May 5, 1868; 4" x 5 1/4"; Murray, Andrew, 1812-1878
    Kensington, A.L.S. 1p. and add.
  - Letter to John [L.] LeConte, May 5, 1868; Watts, J. Howe
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, May 13, 1868; 7 3/4" x 9 3/4"; Walsh, B. D. (Benjamin Dann), 1808-1869
    Rock Island, Ill., A.L.S. 2p. Notes by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, May 14, 1868; 8" x 10"; Yardley, Thomas W., 1826-1900
    Cincinnati, A.L.S. 1p.
  - Letter to John [L. Le Conte ?], May 19, 1868; 5 3/4" x 7 1/2"; Harden, Jane LeConte
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Cont, May 19, 1868; 5" x 8"; Shimer, Henry
    Mt. Carroll, I11., A.L.S. 2p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to [John L. LeConte], May 21, 1868; de Bouvauloir, H.
  - Letter to [J.L. ?] Le Conte, May 28, 1868; 5" x 8"; Wright, W. W. (William Wierman) 1824-1882
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, May 30, 1868; 7 3/4" x 9 3/4"; Walsh, B. D. (Benjamin Dann), 1808-1869
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, May 31, 1868; 5 1/2" x 7"; Shimer, Henry
    Mt. Carroll, I11., A.L.S. 2p.
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, June 7, 1868; 7 3/4" x 9 3/4"; Walsh, B. D. (Benjamin Dann), 1808-1869
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, July 8, 1868; 9-1/4x7-1/4; Wright, W. W. (William Wierman) 1824-1882
    Harrisburg, A.L.S. 2p. (see Le Conte papers.) Entomology. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to [J.L.?] Le Conte, July 12, 1868; 7" x 9 1/4"; Wright, W. W. (William Wierman) 1824-1882
    Harrisburg, A.L.S. 2p.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], July 20, [1868]; 4" x 5 1/4"; Matthews, A. (Andrew), 1815-1897
    A.L.S. 4p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, July 22, 1868; 7 3/4" x 9 3/4"; Walsh, B. D. (Benjamin Dann), 1808-1869
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], July 29, 1868; 5" x 8"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, Aug. 15, 1868; 8" x 10"; Walsh, B. D. (Benjamin Dann), 1808-1869
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, Aug. 28, 1868; 8" x 10"; Walsh, B. D. (Benjamin Dann), 1808-1869
  - Letter to John L. Leconte, Sept. 11, 1868; 5 1/4" x 8"; Sallé, Aug., (Auguste), 1820-1896
  - Letter to [John L. LeConte], Oct. 21, 1868; Brown, Edwin
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte ?], Nov. 2, 1868; 5 1/4" x 8"; Chaudoir, M. de (Maximilien), baron, 1817-1881
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], Nov. 17, 1868; 8" x 10"; Sonne, Charles
  - Letter to John L. Leconte, Nov. 19, 1868; 5" x 8"; Sallé, Aug., (Auguste), 1820-1896
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, Nov. 22, 1868; 5" x 8"; Gibbs, George, 1815-1873
  - Letter to J[ohn] L. LeConte, Dec. 9, 1868; Bethune, Charles H.
    Appreciation for any copies of LeConte's works to supplement the Entomological Society's small library.
  - Letter to [John L. Le Conte], Dec. 9, 1868; 11x8-1/2; Smithsonian Institution.
    Washington, L.S.: Joseph Henry. 1p. (see Le Conte papers.) Sends him diatomacaea remains for study. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, Dec. 12, 1868; 5" x 8"; Grier, Robert Cooper, 1794-1870
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, Jan. 29, 1869; 8" x 10"; Walsh, B. D. (Benjamin Dann), 1808-1869
  - Letter to J. L. Lejonte [sic], Feb. 3, 1869; Fellows, Arthur
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, Feb. 14, 1869; 8" x 10"; Walsh, B. D. (Benjamin Dann), 1808-1869
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte ?], Feb. 15, 1869; 5 1/4" x 8 1/4"; Lacordaire, Théodore, 1801-1870
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, Feb. 20, 1869; 8" x 10"; Walsh, B. D. (Benjamin Dann), 1808-1869
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, March 15, 1869; 5" x 8"; Grier, Robert Cooper, 1794-1870
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, March 19, 1869; 8" x 10"; Walsh, B. D. (Benjamin Dann), 1808-1869
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte ?], April 2, 1869; 5 1/4" x 8 1/4"; Lacordaire, Théodore, 1801-1870
    Liège, (?) A.L.S. 4p. In French
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, April 19, 1869; 5 1/4" x 8"; Murray, Andrew, 1812-1878
  - Letter to John L. Leconte, June 4, 1869; 5" x 8"; Sallé, Aug., (Auguste), 1820-1896
  - Letter to [John L. LeConte], June 19, 1869; Chapin, F.
  - Letter to [J. Peter] Lesley, June 28, 1869; Hall, James
  - Indenture to the Pennsylvania Company for Insurance on Lives and Granting Annuities, June 11, 1869; 12-1/2x8; Le Conte, John L. (John Lawrence), 1825-1883
    D.S. 3p. Mutilated. (see Le Conte Papers.)
  - Letter to J.D. Perry, July 11, 1869; 5 1/4" x 5 1/2"; Le Conte, John L. (John Lawrence), 1825-1883
  - Letter to John L. Leconte, July 16, 1869; 5 1/4" x 8"; Sallé, Aug., (Auguste), 1820-1896
  - Letter to John [L. Le Conte], July 24, 1869; 5" x 8"; LeConte, Joseph, 1823-1901
    Savannah, Ga., A.L.S. 2p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to the Kansas Pacific R.R. co., Sept. 20, 1869; 5" x 8"; Le Conte, John L. (John Lawrence), 1825-1883
  - Letter to [J.L.] Leconte, Sept. 24, 1869; 5 1/4" x 8 1/4"; Murray, Andrew, 1812-1878
    Kensington, A.L.S. 2p.
  - Letter of attorney to Aubrey H. Smith, Oct. 4, 1869; LeConte, John L., (John Lawrence), 1825-1883
  - Letter to [John L. Le Conte], Nov. 16, 1869; 6x4; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
    A.L.S. 2p. Incomplete. (see Le Conte papers.) Entomology. Death of Walsh.
  - Notes in reply to Dr. Horn's letter, Dec. 17, 1869; LeConte, John L., (John Lawrence), 1825-1883
  - Letter to John L. LeConte, 1869; Sharswood, William, 1836-1905
  - Letter to J. [L?] Leconte, Jan. 2, 1870; 4" x 6 1/4"; Wallace, Alfred Russel, 1823-1913
  - Account with John L. LeConte, Jan. 24, 1870; Smith, Aubrey H.
  - Letter to Aubrey H. Smith, Feb. 7, 1870; Venvill, William
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], Feb. 14, 1870; 5 1/4" x 8 1/4"; Sallé, Aug., (Auguste), 1820-1896
    Paris, A.L.S. 2p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], Feb. 16, 1870; 5 1/4" x 8 1/4"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 6p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to A[ubrey] H. Smith, Feb. 19, 1870; Venvill, William
  - Letter to Jo[h]n L. LeConte, Feb. 22, 1870; Smith, Aubrey H.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte ?], March 14, 1870; 5 1/4" x 8"; Sallé, Aug., (Auguste), 1820-1896
  - Letter to Aubrey [H. Smith], March 15, 1870; 5 1/4" x 8 1/4"; Le Conte, John L. (John Lawrence), 1825-1883
    Algiers, A.L. 2p.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], March 24, 1870; 5 1/4" x 8 1/4"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 8p.
  - Letter to J. C. Reiff, Apr. 18, 1870; Smith, Aubrey H.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], April 25, [1870 ?]; 5 1/4" x 8 1/4"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 6p.
  - Letter to A[ubrey] H. Smith, May 6, 1870; 8x5-1/4; Verrvill, William
    A.L.S. 3p. (see Le Conte papers.) Business of J.L.Le Conte.
  - Letter to J[ohn] L. Le Conte, May 10, 1870; 8x5; Smith, Aubrey H.
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. (see Le Conte papers) Business.
  - Letter to J[ohn] L. Le Conte, Geneva, Switzerland, May 17, 1870; 8-1/4x5; Smith, Aubrey H.
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 4p. (see Le Conte papers.) Business. Concerning memberships in the Academy of Natural Sciences. Originally B L493.4
  - Letter to [John L. LeConte], May 20, 1870; Carlier, Auguste, 1803-1890
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], June, 1871; 5 1/4" x 8 1/4"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 4p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to Jno. L. Le Conte, July 5, 1870; 5" x 8"; Smith, Aubrey H.
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 4p. and enc. - 1p.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], July 26, [1870]; 5 1/2" x 8 1/2"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
  - Letter to A. H. Smith, Aug. 7, 1870; 8x5; Verrvill, William
    New York, L. 2p. (see Le Conte papers.) Business accounts of J.L.Le Conte.
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, Aug. 9, 1870; 8x5; Smith, Aubrey H.
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 4p. (see Le Conte papers Business.) Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to A.H. Smith, Aug.15, 1870; 5" x 8"; Verrvill, William
    New York, Copy of L. 1p. On same sheet with letter from A.H.Smith to J.L. Le Conte, Aug.16,1870.
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, Aug.16, 1870; 5" x 8"; Smith, Aubrey H.
    Phila., A.L.S. 2p. Contains also a copy of a letter from Wm. Verrvill to A.H. Smith, Aug. 15,1870.
  - Letter to John L. Leconte, Sept. 17, 1870; 5 1/4" x 8 1/4"; Agassiz, Alexander, 1835-1910
    Geneva, A.L.S. 2p.
  - Letter to Jo[h]n L. Le Conte, Sept. 22, 1870; 8x5; Smith, Aubrey H.
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 4p. (see Le Conte papers Forwards money. News of Philadelphia. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to J[ohn] L. Le Conte, Sept. 27, 1870; 8x5; Smith, Aubrey H.
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 3p. (see Le Conte papers Finances. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to A.H. Smith, Sept. 28, 1870; 5" x 8"; Verrvill, William
    New York, Copy of L. 2p.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], Oct. 5, 1870; 5 1/2" x 8 1/2"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
  - Letter to Jno. L. Le Conte, Oct. 21, 1870; 5" x 8"; Smith, Aubrey H.
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 7p.
  - Letter to A.H. Smith, Nov. 7, 1870; 5 1/4" x 8"; Verrvill, William
  - Letter to Jno. L. Le Conte, Nov. 10, 1870; 5 1/4" x 8"; Smith, Aubrey H.
    Philadelphia A.L.S. 4p.
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, Nov. 11, 1870; 5 1/4" x 8"; Smith, Aubrey H.
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 4p.
  - Letter to Mrs. H. G. Le Conte, Feb. 7, 1871; 5" x 8"; Smith, Aubrey H.
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, March 10, 1871; 5" x 8"; Smith, Aubrey H.
  - Letter to Helen [LeConte], Mar. 28, 1871; LeConte, Sarah
    Signed "Sarah" (Joseph LeConte's daughter?) and discusses business matters with Aubrey [Smith], marriage and other interpersonal news.
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, April 3, 1871; 5" x 8"; Smith, Aubrey H.
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 3p.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], April 9, 1871; 4 1/2" x 7"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], April 20, 1871; 5 1/2" x 8 1/2"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], May 15, 1871; 5 1/2" x 8 1/2"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
  - Letter to [John L.] Le Conte, May 19, 1871; 8x5; Fay, Alec Alexander
    London, A.L.S. 2P. (see Le Conte papers Friendly letter. Concerning English insects. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, May 23, 1871; 5" x 8"; Smith, Aubrey H.
  - Letter to John L. Leconte, May 24, 1871; 7x4-1/2; Westwood, J. O. (John Obadiah), 1805-1893
    Oxford, Eng. A.L.S. 3p. (see Le Conte papers.) Will be glad to have him visit. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to [John L.] Le Conte, May 25, 1871; 7x4-1/2; Bates, Henry Walter, 1825-1892
    A.L.S. 3p. (see Le Conte papers.) Hopes to see him when he returns from the country. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to [John L.] Leconte, May 29, 1871; 7x4-1/2; Sclater, Philip Lutley, 1829-1913
    London, A.L.S. 2p. (see Le Conte papers.) Hopes to see him in England. Originally B L493.2
  - Directions for visiting his home, May, [1871]; 8x5; Owen, Richard, 1804-1892
    A.D. 1p.,end.by J.L.Le Conte. (see Le Conte papers.) Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to J[ohn L.] Leconte, June 4, 1871; 4-1/2x3-1/2; Westwood, J. O. (John Obadiah), 1805-1893
    Oxford, Eng., A.L.S. 3p. (see Le Conte papers.) Coleoptera. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to Jno. L. Le Conte, June 8, 1871; 5" x 8"; Smith, Aubrey H.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], June 10, 1871; 5" x 8"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 6p. End. by J.L. Le conte.
  - Letter to [John L. Le Conte], June 12, 1871; 8-1/4x5-1/4; Sallé, Aug., (Auguste), 1820-1896
    Paris, A.L.S. 2p. In French. (see Le Conte papers.) Entomology. Hopes to see him. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to [John L. Le Conte], June 24, 1871; 8-1/4x5; Faure, Albert
    Caen, A.L.S. 3p. In French. (see Le Conte papers.) Entomology. Friendly letter. Refers to Horn and Smithsonian. Originally B L493.4
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], June 29, 1871; 5" x 8"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 6P. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Receipt to [John L. LeConte], Jul. 1, 1871; Wittmann, N.
  - Letter to [John L.] Le Conte, July 3, 1871; 4-1/2x3-1/2; Murray, Andrew, 1812-1878
    A.L.S. 2p. (see Le Conte papers.) Is busy and asks him to postpone his departure to have dinner with a group: Osten-Sacken and Westwood may be there. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], July 7, 1871; 4 1/2" x 7"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
  - List of insects sent to Dr. Horn, July 8, 1871; 8x5; Bell, W. A.
    D.in hand of J.L.Le Conte. 1p. (see Le Conte papers.)
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, July 16, 1871; 5" x 8"; Smith, Aubrey H.
  - Letter to Jo[h]n L. Le Conte, Philadelphia, July 17, 1871; 9-1/2x5-1/2; Ashmead, William Harris
    Jacksonville, Fla., A.L.S 3p. (see Le Conte papers.) Thanks for his Publication on entomology. Originally B L493.4
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], July 22, 1871; 5" x 8"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], July 31, 1871; 4 1/2" x 7"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], Aug. 24, 1871; 4 1/2" x 7"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
  - Letter to [John L. LeConte], Aug. 24, 1871; Fauvel, Albert Auguste, 1851-
  - Account with W[illiam] Venvill, Aug. 1871 - Feb. 1872; On same sheet as Smith's statement of account with LeConte.; LeConte, John L., (John Lawrence), 1825-1883
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], Sept. 8, 1871; 5 1/4" x 8 1/4"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
  - Letter to Jo[h]n L. LeConte, Sept. 25, 1871; Mayer, Edward Rodman, 1823-1891
  - Letter to [John L. LeConte], Sept. 30, 1871; Meyers, E. M.
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, Sept., 1871; 4 1/2" x 7"; Matthews, A. (Andrew), 1815-1897
    [ca.]. A.L.S. 4p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], Oct. 3, 1871; 5" x 8"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 5p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to J[ohn] L. Le Conte, Oct. 12, 1871; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Bulard
    A.L.S. 2p.and end. (see Le Conte papers.) Wishes to visit him and asks mailing directions.
  - Letter to J[ohn L. Le Conte], Nov. 5, 1871; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Meyers, E. M.
    Brussels, A.L.S. 4p.,end. In French. (see Le Conte papers.) Entomological news.
  - Statement of account with J[ohn] L. LeConte, Nov. 10, 1871; On same sheet as LeConte's account with Venvill.; Smith, Aubrey H, ca. 1813-1891
  - Letter to J.L. Le Conte, Nov. 14, 1871; 4 1/2" x 7"; Waterhouse, Charles Owen, 1843-1917
    British museum, A.L.S. 2p.
  - Letter to [J.L.] Leconte, Nov. 16, 1871; 5" x 8"; Boucard, A.
    London, A.L.S. 2p.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], Nov. 20, 1871; 5" x 8"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], Dec. 18, 1871; 5" x 8"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, Dec. 31, 1871; 5" x 8"; Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1837-1911
    ---- A.L.S. 2p.
  - Letter to [J.L.] Leconte, Dec., 1871; 4 1/2" x 7"; Crotch, George R.
    [ca. A.L.S. 3p. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to [J.L.] Leconte, Jan. 5, 1872; 5" x 8"; Sallé, Aug., (Auguste), 1820-1896
    Paris, A.L.S. 3p. In French. End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], Jan. 23, 1872; 4" x 6 1/4"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 4p End. by J.L. Le Conte.
  - Letter to A[ubrey] H. Smith, Feb. 8, 1872; 8x5-1/4; Verrvill, William
    New York, A.L.S. 2p.,with P.S.by J.L.Le Conte; Rome, March 3, 1872. (see Le Conte papers.) Business.
  - Letter to J[ohn] L. Le Conte, Feb. 10, 1872; 8x5-1/4; Smith, Aubrey H.
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 4p.,end. (see Le Conte papers.) Business.
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, Feb. 14, [1872]; 5 1/4" x 8 1/2"; Matthews, A. (Andrew), 1815-1897
  - Letter to [John L. Le Conte], Feb. 27, 1872; 8-1/4x5-1/4; Fauvel, Albert Auguste, 1851-
    Caen, A.L.S. 3p.,end. In French. (see Le Conte papers.) Entomology.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], March 6, 1872; 4 1/2" x 7"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 4p. End. by J.L. Le conte.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], April 6, 1872; 4" x 6 1/4"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
  - Letter to [J.L.] Le Conte, April 16, [1872]; 5" x 8"; Frazer, Charlotte Cave
  - Letter to Aubrey H. Smith, May 7, 1872; 5 1/4" x 8"; Verrvill, William
    New York, A.L.S. 3p.
  - Letter to John [L.] Le Conte, May 9, 1872; 8x5-1/4; Smith, Aubrey H.
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 5p.,end. (see Le Conte papers.) Business. Originally B L493.2
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], May 11, 1872; 5" x 8"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], June 2, 1872; 4 1/2" x 7"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
  - Letter to [John L. LeConte], June 3, 1872; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
  - Letter to John L. Le Conte, Lausanne, Switzerland, June 6, 1872; 8x5-1/4; Keath, John Meredith
    Paris, A.L.S. 3p. (see Le Conte papers.) Asks about elections of certain men and their notices, which might have been sent through the State Department. John Lindsley, H.R.Phelps, and W[illia]m Tilghman. 4p.,end. (see George Clymer papers.)
  - Letter to [John L. Le Conte], June 7, 1872; 8-1/4x5-1/4; Meyers, E. M.
    Brussels, A.L.S. 4p., In French. (see Le Conte papers.) Entomological news.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], June 18, 1872; 4 1/2" x 7" and 4 1/2" x 4"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
  - Letter to [John L. Le Conte], June 18, 1872; 8-1/4x5-1/4; Retsema, C.
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Le Conte papers.) Agrees to his publication on entomology.
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], June 24, 1872; 4 1/2" x 7"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897
  - Letter to [Mrs.] Helen [LeConte], July 3, 1872
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], July 9, 1872; 3 3/4" x 6"; Chaudoir, M. de (Maximilien), baron, 1817-1881
  - Letter to [J.L. Le Conte], July 10, 1872; 4" x 6 1/4"; Horn, George Henry, 1840-1897